sidetick.tv 2016-11-06

# SideTick TV - Internet Television!

**SIDETICK TV PRIVACY POLICY - [Updated 03.02.15** **]**   
Sidetick.tv ("SideTick TV") would like to thank you for visiting our website SideTick TV located at http://sidetick.tv (the "Website"). Throughout this Privacy Policy, SideTick TV may be referred to as "we", "us", or "our" and you, the user of the Website, may be referred to as "you" or "your".   
**1\. Purpose** ****  
The purpose of this policy is to explain to you our business practices that we have in place regarding the information you provide to us online at this Website and the various choices that are available to you regarding the ways that we utilize this information. Sidetick TV is a social networking site that encourages users to share information with other users. This privacy policy is intended to explain to you how we use information you submit to us over the site. In addition to sharing information with SideTick TV, you may share personal information with other users based on your profile settings and affirmative decisions to participate in forums, discussions, and other services offered through the Website.   
**2** . **Minors**   
This Website is not intended for use by minors under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to use the Website. We do not knowingly collect any information pertaining to minors under the age of 13. Parents and guardians should closely monitor the Internet activities of their children and we encourage such adult supervision and active participation which support a positive Internet learning experience.   
**3** . **More Information**   
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or would like additional information on our privacy practices, please feel free to contract us directly at [cservice@sidetick.tv](mailto:cservice@sidetick.tv) or write to: SideTick, LLC, 5887 Glenridge Drive, Suite 400, Atlanta Georgia 30328.   
**4\. What information do we collect?** ****  
**a. Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
When you visit this Website, our servers automatically collect certain web site usage information. Website usage information is non-identifying information that describes how our visitors use and navigate this Web Site, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays. We also collect the information automatically sent to us by your browser, such as browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting this Web Site, and IP address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet, which web servers use to identify where to send the information your computer requests. We may use IP addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the use of this Web Site. We also may determine the technology available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page. We may disclose non-identifying user information, such as aggregated statistics, to third parties for a variety of purposes, including describing our services, marketing, and providing a better user experience on this Website.   
**b. Personally Identifiable Information** ****  
We collect personally identifiable information about you. For example, we may collect your name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number and date of birth when you register or make a purchase at this Website. You may also provide us with highly sensitive personal information through your profile or other services on the Website, including, but not limited to, where you work, pictures, relationships, and political and religious views. Additionally, we collect information about your use of SideTick TV services, including, but not limited, your activity on SideTick TV, your viewing of movies and tv shows, your ratings and reviews of movies and tv shows, payment history and communications.   
We also collect information that you provide us in response to questions we ask of you while visiting this Website regarding interests you may have about certain products and services offered by some of our advertising partners. This information is collected when you provide it to us, even when you complete some, but not all, of the registration process.   
Furthermore, we may collect personally identifiable information about you through surveys, polls, forums, and other services provided through the Website.   
**5\. How Do We Use Your Information?** ****  
We use your _non-personally identifiable information_ that you submit for Website design and content improvements and to allow us the opportunity to personalize your experience on the Internet, in particular, your return visits to the Website. Personalizing your Internet experience allows us to present you with offers for products and services that we believe might be of interest to you. We also use this type of information in our analysis of the overall usage of our Website by you and other users. This type of data describes the demographics of users of the Website including each user's usage and characteristics compiled and reported as a group rather than on an individual basis. To the extent allowable by law, we reserve the right to share non-personally identifiable information collected from you with third parties. Your use of the Website shall be considered your approval to our sharing this non-personally identifiable information to third parties.   
We do not share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties, except as provided for in this Privacy Policy and the SideTick TV Terms of Service.   
We use _personally identifiable information_ to provide the social networking services over this Website. These uses include, but are not limited to, contacting you about the services on our Website, billing you for certain services, or providing offers for products and services offered by SideTick TV, its affiliates, or trusted third-parties. SideTick TV uses the information it collects on the Website to provide the Website and affiliated services to you and may use such information to enhance the value of the Website. SideTick TV may also use information about you in the aggregate for marketing and promotional purposes, to improve the content of our Website or services, or to notify you about updates to our Website. We may also allow publicly-shared information to be collected and used by search engines, such as Bing and Google. We may collect publically-shared information in any legally permissible manner.   
We will also collect your information to provide a better viewing experience by using your information to personalize the services offered to you to reflect your interests, to provide recommendations on movies and tv shows that you may enjoy, to track your viewing habits, to provide localized content, and to efficiently respond to your requests and inquiries.    
SideTick TV will use information about you to contact you through email and notices posted on the Website. SideTick TV will also contact you to authorize other users to access your networks and information. You may block any user for any reason or for no reason by pressing the 'Block" button located at their profile homepage which shall restrict their ability to access your profile. **** We send all new users a welcoming email to verify password and user name. Established members may also receive information on products, services, events, and publications.   
We will use information we collect about you to serve advertisements to you. We may also use your information we collect about you to serve advertisements through email and other channels to you through one or more listed marketing partners, that among them is Diversiosity, LLC.   
Information about other users and non-users that you provide SideTick TV may be used like information collected by SideTick TV directly, and is subject only to this Privacy Policy.   
In the event that it is determined that the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, 15 U.S.C. 6802 (hereinafter the "GLB Act") is applicable to us and the services we provide, this policy shall serve as the initial "Privacy Notice" which we are required to furnish to you in accordance with the provisions of the GLB Act. Your submission of your personal information shall serve as your acknowledgment of receipt of the required notice as well as granting your consent for us to forward your annual notice of the Privacy Policy by posting the same at this Website and/or transmitting the same to you via email communication.   
We may partner with third-parties to provide services to Users, such as credit card processing or course materials. We share some information collected over the Website - including personally identifiable information - that such third-parties need to provide these services. Such third-parties may only use any information from SideTick TV to provide these third-party services to you. Such third-parties are governed by their own privacy and security policies. We do not sell, share, exchange, rent, or otherwise provide personally identifiable information about our Users to third-parties for their marketing purposes.   
We may share personally identifiable information about you when (i) we reasonably believe that this Website has been used in connection with any illegal act(s) or commission of a crime, (ii) information about you is the subject of a subpoena issued to us or is required to be disclosed as a matter of law or pursuant to some other order issued by a court of law, (iii) information about you is responsive to a due diligence inquiry made by a prospective purchaser as part of a merger or acquisition of our assets or ownership interests, or (iv) the need for your information is based on public or personal safety concerns; to detect or deter actual or potential fraud, abuse, or other misuse of the Website or against SideTick TV or another third-party; or to protect against potential losses, as determined in our sole discretion.   
If the ownership of all or substantially all of this Website or the company changes, we reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information to the new owner(s). In the event of such a transfer, your information remains subject to the promises made in the then-current version of this Privacy Policy.   
If you join a community in SideTick TV, your information will be shared with the leader of that community. By joining a community you consent to this sharing of information and to receive communications from the community.s leader.   
When you convert your Tickbucks into cash, your information may be shared with others, including other SideTick TV members and taxing authorities, disclosing that such cash payment has been made to you.   
**6\. You May Also Share Information with Others** ****  
As a social networking site, you may disclose personally identifiable information through your profile or through your use of services on this Website to other users or to the general public. You may change your settings to limit the amount of profile information you share with others. By participating in or otherwise using the Website, you consent to allowing other Users that you have authorized to access and see information, including personally identifiable information, about you that you have provided to the Site. Each user controls how much personally identifiable information is shared with others, except your name is always shared with others on the Website. Other than your name, which is shared with everyone on the Website at all times, you have complete control over how much and when personally identifiable information is available to any other user. You should also be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to provide as part of participating in the Website - including responding to emails from other Users, participating in forums or message boards, or responding to surveys - may be read, collected, or used by Users, or forwarded to non-Users. You should exercise caution when using chat rooms, forums, or other services on this Website where personally identifiable information may be shared with other users or the general public. ****  
**7\. "Cookies"**  
This Website may also utilize cookies, text files that are placed on your computer's browser which indicate your preferences, which helps us improve the Website and personalize your Internet experience. You may learn more about cookies by visiting www.cookiecentral.com. You may still visit our Website even if you decide that you do not wish to allow cookies; however, certain functionality may be lost if you do not accept cookies. For example, the "remember me" function on the log-in page would not be operable.   
**8\. Third-Party Advertisement and Sites**   
The advertisements that appear on and third-party sites linked from this Website are not endorsed by us. We make no guarantee regarding the accuracy of the information contained in these third-party advertisements and sites. Responsibility for such ad and site content remains solely with the third party.   
You may choose to share information with third-party advertisers not associated with the Website. Such sharing through their on-site offers is entirely up to you.   
Please be aware that each of these independent third party advertisers and sites may have their own Privacy Policy, which describes how each third-party collects and uses your information. We recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies for each third-party site and remember that this Privacy Policy only applies to the information you submit to us at this Website.   
**9\. What security measures do we take to safeguard your information?** ****  
The information that you submit to us at this Website is safeguarded by us utilizing industry standard security measures in an effort to protect such data from unauthorized access or disclosure whether online or off-line. Please keep in mind that the security of any information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed and you submit your personal information at your own risk. In the unlikely event that the security of your information is compromised, we will notify you as quickly as is reasonably practicable consistent with the needs of federal or local authorities and law enforcement and following determination of the scope of the security breach and appropriate remedial measures have been initiated to mitigate the damages. You agree and hereby affirmatively consent to receive such security breach notification via email to the address you provide to us at registration.   
We protect the information that you submit to us online using SSL encryption software. Off-line your information is shared internally only with our employees who have a "need to know" in order to perform their assigned duties. Access to any of your information is prohibited to all others.   
**10\. What choices are available to you regarding our use of your information?** ****  
If you wish to no longer receive future email communications pertaining to this Website [Click Here](http://www.sidetick.tv/unsubscribe.php?p=1010) and we will promptly honor your opt-out request.   
If you no longer wish to receive future email communications pertaining to this Website or any other website operated by us or any of our business divisions, you may globally opt-out by [Clicking Here](http://www.sidetick.tvsidetick.tv/unsubscribe.php?p=-666).   
If you are an existing member or become a member but wish to not receive SideTick TV system notifications, you will also need to indicate your opt-out preferences by unmarking the boxes on your [account preferences page](http://www.sidetick.tv/account_preferences.php).   
Although SideTick TV strives to honor your opt-out request promptly, please allow ten (10) business days to process your request. During such processing time, it is possible that you may continue to receive communications from us.   
A user can decide to quit SideTick TV by simply selecting the 'Profile' tab located on the Home Page and then selecting 'Account Settings' and then selecting 'Delete Account', the fourth tab on the following page. On the next page select 'Delete My Account'.   
Your personal identifying information is retained by us in our archives for as long as we deem appropriate, which may include indefinitely, showing, in part, compliance with applicable law and having record of the termination. Your information is not shared with affiliates.   
**11\. Copies of Information; Updating and Correcting Information We Have Collected**   
You may obtain copies of information we collect upon by sending a written request to [cservice@sidetick.tv](mailto:cservice@sidetick.tv). You may update and make any corrections to your profile if and when necessary by selecting 'Account Settings' from the 'Profile' pull down menu. ****  
**12\. Foreign Privacy**  
By using the Website, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.   
**13\. Submitting Your Information Using Your Electronic Signature** ****  
By submitting your information and agreeing to the terms contained in this Privacy Policy, you agree to conduct business electronically in accordance with the federal Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act (E-Sign), 15 U.S.C.A. 7001-7031 (Supp. 2001). You further understand that transactions and/or signatures in records may not be denied legal effect solely because they are conducted, executed or prepared in electronic form and that if a law requires or permits a record or signature to be in writing, an electronic record or signature satisfies that requirement. You acknowledge and freely consent that submitting your information shall constitute a binding electronic signature under the laws of the United States. You further agree that you will use your electronic signature to accept electronic records pertaining to the Website, its products and/or services which includes in part this Privacy Policy. Additionally, you agree and consent to receive and to be legally bound by other information sent electronically, which may include certain disclosures which we might be required to make in accordance with federal, state or local law or regulation which may be issued to you electronically.   
**14\. Amendments and Updates to this Privacy Policy** ****  
By accessing this Website, you are agreeing to each provision of this Privacy Policy, which may be modified by us at any time. Any change to this Privacy Policy shall become effective immediately upon posting on the Website and your continued use of the Website. Bookmark this page and check it periodically for any changes to this Privacy Policy.   
**15\. States' Laws Take Precedence on Limitation of Liability** ****  
**Some states have laws which prohibit certain limitations from liability, so the limitations expressed in this Privacy Policy and other SideTick TV documents and policies may not apply to you. For residents of those select states, we recommend that you seek advice from legal counsel regarding the limitations applicable and acceptable in your jurisdiction.**
